[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What time-savings advantage is offered with the use of Amazon Rekognition?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon Rekognition provides automatic watermarking of images.",
      "Amazon Rekognition provides automatic detection of objects appearing in pictures.",
      "Amazon Rekognition provides the ability to resize millions of images automatically.",
      "Amazon Rekognition uses Amazon Mechanical Turk to allow humans to bid on object detection jobs."
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "When comparing AWS with on-premises Total Cost of Ownership (TCO), what costs are included?",
    "options": [
      "Data center security",
      "Business analysis",
      "Project management",
      "Operating system administration"
    ],
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "According to the AWS shared responsibility model, what is AWS responsible for?",
    "options": [
      "Configuring Amazon VPC",
      "Managing application code",
      "Maintaining application traffic",
      "Managing the network infrastructure"
    ],
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Which service should be used to estimate the costs of running a new project on AWS?",
    "options": [
      "AWS TCO Calculator",
      "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator",
      "AWS Cost Explorer API",
      "AWS Budgets"
    ],
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Which AWS tool will identify security groups that grant unrestricted Internet access to a limited list of ports?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Organizations",
      "AWS Trusted Advisor",
      "AWS Usage Report",
      "Amazon EC2 dashboard"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Which AWS service can be used to generate alerts based on an estimated monthly bill?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Config",
      "Amazon CloudWatch",
      "AWS X-Ray",
      "AWS CloudTrail"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which Amazon EC2 pricing model offers the MOST significant discount when compared to On-Demand Instances?",
    "options": [
      "Partial Upfront Reserved Instances for a 1-year term",
      "All Upfront Reserved Instances for a 1-year term",
      "All Upfront Reserved Instances for a 3-year term",
      "No Upfront Reserved Instances for a 3-year term"
    ],
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which of the following is the responsibility of AWS?",
    "options": [
      "Setting up AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) users and groups",
      "Physically destroying storage media at end of life",
      "Patching guest operating systems",
      "Configuring security settings on Amazon EC2 instances"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of using AWS?",
    "options": [
      "AWS audits user data.",
      "Data is automatically secure.",
      "There is no guessing on capacity needs.",
      "AWS manages compliance needs."
    ],
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which AWS service would a customer use with a static website to achieve lower latency and high transfer speeds?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Lambda",
      "Amazon DynamoDB Accelerator",
      "Amazon Route 53",
      "Amazon CloudFront"
    ],
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Which services manage and automate application deployments on AWS? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
      "AWS CodeCommit",
      "AWS Data Pipeline",
      "AWS CloudFormation",
      "AWS Config"
    ],
    "answer": "AD"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "A user wants guidance on possible savings when migrating from on-premises to AWS. <br/> Which tool is suitable for this scenario?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Budgets",
      "Cost Explorer",
      "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator",
      "AWS Well-Architected Tool"
    ],
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Which principles are used to architect applications for reliability on the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "Design for automated failure recovery",
      "Use multiple Availability Zones",
      "Manage changes via documented processes",
      "Test for moderate demand to ensure reliability",
      "Backup recovery to an on-premises environment"
    ],
    "answer": "AB"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What tasks should a customer perform when that customer suspects an AWS account has been compromised? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "Rotate passwords and access keys.",
      "Remove MFA tokens.",
      "Move resources to a different AWS Region.",
      "Delete AWS CloudTrail Resources.",
      "Contact AWS Support."
    ],
    "answer": "AE"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What is an example of high availability in the AWS Cloud?",
    "options": [
      "Consulting AWS technical support at any time day or night",
      "Ensuring an application remains accessible, even if a resource fails",
      "Making any AWS service available for use by paying on demand",
      "Deploying in any part of the world using AWS Regions"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "Which AWS security service protects applications from distributed denial of service attacks with always-on detection and automatic inline mitigations?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon Inspector",
      "AWS Web Application Firewall (AWS WAF)",
      "Elastic Load Balancing (ELB)",
      "AWS Shield"
    ],
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "A company wants to monitor the CPU usage of its Amazon EC2 resources. <br/> Which AWS service should the company use?",
    "options": [
      "AWS CloudTrail",
      "Amazon CloudWatch",
      "AWS Cost and Usage report",
      "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What is an AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) role?",
    "options": [
      "A user associated with an AWS resource",
      "A group associated with an AWS resource",
      "An entity that defines a set of permissions for use with an AWS resource",
      "An authentication credential associated with a multi-factor authentication (MFA) token"
    ],
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What are the advantages of Reserved Instances? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "They provide a discount over on-demand pricing.",
      "They provide access to additional instance types.",
      "They provide additional networking capability.",
      "Customers can upgrade instances as new types become available.",
      "Customers can reserve capacity in an Availability Zone."
    ],
    "answer": "AE"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "How do Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling groups help achieve high availability for a web application?",
    "options": [
      "They automatically add more instances across multiple AWS Regions based on global demand of the application.",
      "They automatically add or replace instances across multiple Availability Zones when the application needs it.",
      "They enable the application's static content to reside closer to end users.",
      "They are able to distribute incoming requests across a tier of web server instances."
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "How can one AWS account use Reserved Instances from another AWS account?",
    "options": [
      "By using Amazon EC2 Dedicated Instances",
      "By using AWS Organizations consolidated billing",
      "By using the AWS Cost Explorer tool",
      "By using AWS Budgets"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "A customer runs an On-Demand Amazon Linux EC2 instance for 3 hours, 5 minutes, and 6 seconds. <br/> For how much time will the customer be billed?",
    "options": [
      "3 hours, 5 minutes",
      "3 hours, 5 minutes, and 6 seconds",
      "3 hours, 6 minutes",
      "4 hours"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "Which of the following AWS services provide compute resources? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "AWS Lambda",
      "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)",
      "AWS CodeDeploy",
      "Amazon Glacier",
      "AWS Organizations"
    ],
    "answer": "AB"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "Which AWS service enables users to deploy infrastructure as code by automating the process of provisioning resources?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon GameLift",
      "AWS CloudFormation",
      "AWS Data Pipeline",
      "AWS Glue"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "Which AWS services provide a way to extend an on-premises architecture to the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "Amazon EBS",
      "AWS Direct Connect",
      "Amazon CloudFront",
      "AWS Storage Gateway",
      "Amazon Connect"
    ],
    "answer": "BD"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "Which of the following allows users to provision a dedicated network connection from their internal network to AWS?",
    "options": [
      "AWS CloudHSM",
      "AWS Direct Connect",
      "AWS VPN",
      "Amazon Connect"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "Which services use AWS edge locations? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "Amazon CloudFront",
      "AWS Shield",
      "Amazon EC2",
      "Amazon RDS",
      "Amazon ElastiCache"
    ],
    "answer": "A, B"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "Which service would provide network connectivity in a hybrid architecture that includes the AWS Cloud?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon VPC",
      "AWS Direct Connect",
      "AWS Directory Service",
      "Amazon API Gateway"
    ],
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "Which tool can be used to compare the costs of running a web application in a traditional hosting environment to running it on AWS?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Cost Explorer",
      "AWS Budgets",
      "AWS Cost and Usage report",
      "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator"
    ],
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What is the value of using third-party software from AWS Marketplace instead of installing third-party software on Amazon EC2? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "Users pay for software by the hour or month depending on licensing.",
      "AWS Marketplace enables the user to launch applications with 1-Click.",
      "AWS Marketplace data encryption is managed by a third-party vendor.",
      "AWS Marketplace eliminates the need to upgrade to newer software versions.",
      "Users can deploy third-party software without testing."
    ],
    "answer": "AB"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "Which of the following is a cloud architectural design principle?",
    "options": [
      "Scale up, not out.",
      "Loosely couple components.",
      "Build monolithic systems.",
      "Use commercial database software."
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "Under the shared responsibility model; which of the following areas are the customer's responsibility? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "Firmware upgrades of network infrastructure",
      "Patching of operating systems",
      "Patching of the underlying hypervisor",
      "Physical security of data centers",
      "Configuration of the security group"
    ],
    "answer": "BE"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "Which service enables customers to audit and monitor changes in AWS resources?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Trusted Advisor",
      "Amazon GuardDuty",
      "Amazon Inspector",
      "AWS Config"
    ],
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "Which AWS service identifies security groups that allow unrestricted access to a user's AWS resources?",
    "options": [
      "AWS CloudTrail",
      "AWS Trusted Advisor",
      "Amazon CloudWatch",
      "Amazon Inspector"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "According to the AWS shared responsibility model, who is responsible for configuration management?",
    "options": [
      "It is solely the responsibility of the customer.",
      "It is solely the responsibility of AWS.",
      "It is shared between AWS and the customer.",
      "It is not part of the AWS shared responsibility model."
    ],
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "Which AWS service is a content delivery network that securely delivers data, video, and applications to users globally with low latency and high speeds?",
    "options": [
      "AWS CloudFormation",
      "AWS Direct Connect",
      "Amazon CloudFront",
      "Amazon Pinpoint"
    ],
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "Which benefit of the AWS Cloud supports matching the supply of resources with changing workload demands?",
    "options": [
      "Security",
      "Reliability",
      "Elasticity",
      "High availability"
    ],
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "A user is running an application on AWS and notices that one or more AWS-owned IP addresses is involved in a distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack. <br/> Who should the user contact FIRST about this situation?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Premium Support",
      "AWS Technical Account Manager",
      "AWS Solutions Architect",
      "AWS Abuse team"
    ],
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "Which of the following are benefits of hosting infrastructure in the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "There are no upfront commitments.",
      "AWS manages all security in the cloud.",
      "Users have the ability to provision resources on demand.",
      "Users have access to free and unlimited storage.",
      "Users have control over the physical infrastructure."
    ],
    "answer": "AC"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "What AWS service would be used to centrally manage AWS access policies across multiple accounts?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Service Catalog",
      "AWS Config",
      "AWS Trusted Advisor",
      "AWS Organizations"
    ],
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "What is AWS Trusted Advisor?",
    "options": [
      "It is an AWS staff member who provides recommendations and best practices on how to use AWS.",
      "It is a network of AWS partners who provide recommendations and best practices on how to use AWS.",
      "It is an online tool with a set of automated checks that provides recommendations on cost optimization, performance, and security.",
      "It is another name for AWS Technical Account Managers who provide recommendations on cost optimization, performance, and security."
    ],
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "Which AWS service or feature allows a company to visualize, understand, and manage AWS costs and usage over time?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Budgets",
      "AWS Cost Explorer",
      "AWS Organizations",
      "Consolidated billing"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "Which AWS service offers on-demand access to AWS security and compliance reports?",
    "options": [
      "AWS CloudTrail",
      "AWS Artifact",
      "AWS Health",
      "Amazon CloudWatch"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "What are the benefits of using the AWS Cloud for companies with customers in many countries around the world? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "Companies can deploy applications in multiple AWS Regions to reduce latency.",
      "Amazon Translate automatically translates third-party website interfaces into multiple languages.",
      "Amazon CloudFront has multiple edge locations around the world to reduce latency.",
      "Amazon Comprehend allows users to build applications that can respond to user requests in many languages.",
      "Elastic Load Balancing can distribute application web traffic to multiple AWS Regions around the world, which reduces latency."
    ],
    "answer": "AC"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "Which AWS service handles the deployment details of capacity provisioning, load balancing, Auto Scaling, and application health monitoring?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Config",
      "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
      "Amazon Route 53",
      "Amazon CloudFront"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "Which AWS service provides inbound and outbound network ACLs to harden external connectivity to Amazon EC2?",
    "options": [
      "AWS IAM",
      "Amazon Connect",
      "Amazon VPC",
      "Amazon API Gateway"
    ],
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "question": "When a company provisions web servers in multiple AWS Regions, what is being increased?",
    "options": [
      "Coupling",
      "Availability",
      "Security",
      "Durability"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "question": "The pay-as-you-go pricing model for AWS services:",
    "options": [
      "reduces capital expenditures.",
      "requires payment up front for AWS services.",
      "is relevant only for Amazon EC2, Amazon S3, and Amazon RDS.",
      "reduces operational expenditures."
    ],
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "question": "Under the AWS shared responsibility model, AWS is responsible for which security-related task?",
    "options": [
      "Lifecycle management of IAM credentials",
      "Physical security of global infrastructure",
      "Encryption of Amazon EBS volumes",
      "Firewall configuration"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "question": "Which AWS service enables users to consolidate billing across multiple accounts?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon QuickSight",
      "AWS Organizations",
      "AWS Budgets",
      "Amazon Forecast"
    ],
    "answer": "B"
  }
]